portent.com 2014-06-23

# Portent, Inc. Privacy Policy & Terms of Use - Portent

Your privacy is important. The privacy policy outlined below provides information on the data Portent, Inc. collects from you and the ways we protect your data. Please review this policy carefully and contact us if you have any questions.

## We Respect Your Privacy

You may browse our site anonymously. When you place an order or register on our site, we request your name, email address, mailing address, phone number and credit card information as appropriate.

We use cookies and server logs to collect information including your IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of visit. We use this information to personalize your browsing experience and to help us improve site performance. We do not sell this information and it is only shared with third parties as outlined in the following section.

## Your Information is Protected

Your name and contact information are protected by firewalls. More information about how transactions are processed to secure your data is available under the heading, “Your Transaction is Secure.”

At times, we contract service providers to evaluate data or process transactions. Those third parties are not permitted to share your data with outside parties or to use it for any other reason. We will not share your information for any other reason except as required by law.

## Your Email Address is Private

We comply with the Federal Can-Spam Act (15 U.S.C. 7701 et seq.). We use your email only to communicate with you about your order and products or services that may be of interest to you. You can opt out of receiving emails from Portent by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of the email.

## Your Transaction is Secure

Any credit card information you provide is encrypted using SSL before transmission to a secure payment gateway. Your credit card information is not stored on our servers.

## We Comply with US Privacy Protection Acts

We are in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act and will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. We also comply with the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Our website, products and services are all intended for people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Marketing and Advertising

Portent.com uses the [AdRoll display advertising network](http://www.adroll.com/) to collect visitor data on our site and then serve [targeted display ads](http://www.adroll.com/retargeting) to you on other sites. Our partners use technology such as cookies and web beacons to collect this data. For more information or to opt-out of this type of advertising, please visit [AdRoll’s privacy policy](http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy).

Use of our site implies consent to this privacy policy, which is designed for residents of the US. Any changes to the policy will be posted on this page.

## Terms of Use

This Web site is owned and operated by Portent, Inc. for your personal, personal use only.  
Access to and use of this Site are subject to the following terms and conditions.

By using this Site, you agree to be bound by, these terms of use, whether or not you register as a member. By using this site you represent and warrant that you have the right, authority and capacity to enter into this Agreement and to abide by all of the terms and conditions of this Agreement. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of these terms and conditions at any time. Such changes shall be posted on this page of www.portent.com and shall become effective immediately upon posting. Visitors to this Site should periodically check for changes to these terms. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to these terms and conditions (including the Privacy Policy) will mean you accept these changes.

## Refund / Cancellation policy

Portent.com does not accept returns for downloadable eBooks and videos. For services packages, you may cancel within 24 hours of purchase.

If you have any questions about this policy, contact us at:  
506 2nd Ave., Suite 1700  
Seattle, WA 98104  
USA  
206.575.3740

 _This policy was last modified on October 24, 2013_
